Guide to the George Washington University, Office of Student Life records, 1915-2014 RG0115
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Hillel, 1949-2014; RG0115 Series 24; 7.5 Linear Feet (Box 9, Box 7, Box 6, Box 1, Box 5, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2)
  After forty years of relocation to such location as a church building and an office space, Hillel finally found an enduring home on the corner of 23rd and H streets. The site was dedicated on September 14, 1986, in honor of Lester Poretsky and marked the first permanent Hillel House in the District of Columbia. Lelia Imas and Juan Gruner of Imas Gruner A.I.A. and Associates designed the new three level 13,000 square foot structure, which includced a kosher kitchen. The Hillel House officially opened April 17, 1988 and was renamed the Gewirz Center after the late Morris Gewirz, president of the Washington B'nai B'rith Hillel Board of Governors.
  - Original transfer, 1949-1999; Series 24 Subseries 1; 5.5 Linear Feet
    Scope and Contents
    This series consists of the Hillel student organization and includes correspondence, publications, photos, slides, etc. It is organized into the following sub-series: Administration, Alumni Lists, Buildings, Clippings, Correspondence, Exhibit Paper Material, General Information, Publications, Photographs, Exhibit Photographs, Slides, Scrapbook(s) and Artifacts. The materials range in date from 1949-99.
    Arranged alphabetically by original categories.
    - Administrative: Alumni Committee Minutes etc., 1990 ca. (Box SERIES 24 BOX 1, Folder 1)
    - Administrative: Board of Governors, agenda's, lists, minutes (incomplete), 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Administrative: Event Planning (incomplete), 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Administrative: Event Statistics, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Administrative: Facilities Meeting, agenda's and minutes, 03/02/1999-04/30/1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Administrative: Interest Surveys, 1980 ca. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Administrative: List of participants in Hillel's 50th Anniversary Celebration, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Administrative: Strategic Plan, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Administrative: Student Board, list of officers, addresses and nomination forms, 1980 ca. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Administrative: Student Organization Funding Request, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Lists: handwritten (incomplete), 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Lists: Hillel class registries, 1983 ca. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Lists: Jewish Law Student Association [JLSA], 1984 ca.-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Lists: Miscellaneous Scraps, 1970-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Lists: typed (incomplete), 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Buildings: Cornerstone Dedication [1/2], 09/14/1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Buildings: Cornerstone Dedication [2/2], 09/14/1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Buildings: Gewirz Center Dedication, 04/17/1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Buildings: Hillel Building Fund, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Buildings: Hillel House, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Buildings: Mezuzah Dedication, 02/10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Clippings [1/2], 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Clippings [2/2], 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: Hillel-Sponsored all-University Literary Contest, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Clippings: The GW Hatchet and The Washington Jewish Week, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Clippings: Miscellaneous, 1916-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Prospective Students, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous [received], undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous [sent], undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Exhibit Material: An Overview of the Exhibit, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Exhibit Material: Exhibit Script, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Exhibit Material: Labels, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - General Information: Cherry Tree photocopies, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General Information: Jewish Life in Greater Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - General Information: Hillel Material is primarily from the Hillel web site, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - General Information: Israel, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - General Information: Meeting with Aaron Seidman, 05/09/1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Information: Oral Histories, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - General Information: Program in Judaic Studies and events they have sponsored, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Publications: Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Publications: B'nai B'rith Foundation pamphlets, 1940 ca.-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Publications: Calendar of Event (incomplete), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Publications: Commentator, Summer, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Publications: 50th Anniversary Celebration & Reunion Weekend, 04/04/1997-04/06/1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Publications: Hagefen, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Publications: Hillel Bulletin, 01/1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Publications: Hillel's Capital Commentary (incomplete), 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Publications: Hillel brochures/pamphlets/invitations, 1980 ca.-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Publications: Hillelore, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Publications: Hillel Capital [Yearbook], 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Publications: Hillel at G.W.U., [Yearbook], 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publications: The Jewish Historical Society of Greater Washington, brochures and pamphlets, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Publications: The Jewish Star, 03/1997-09/1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Publications: Miscellaneous program flyers, 1980 ca. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Publications: Pamphlets from miscellaneous organizations, 1980 ca.-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Publications: Program Review, News Item Montage Report, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Publications: Shofar Notes, 09/1998-10/1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Publications: Summer Flash, 09/1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Publications: The GW University Hatchet (originals but incomplete), 11/24/53-04/09/54 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Photographs with negatives: American Israel Public Affairs Committee [AIPAC] Conference, 04/28/1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Photographs with negatives: Ben & Jerry's Ice Cream Study Break, 05/01/1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Photographs with negatives: Board Members, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Photographs with negatives: "Come Schmooze with Animals and Jews" National Zoo Trip, 09/08/1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Cornerstone Dedication, 09/14/1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Photographs with negatives: "Dress Your Neighbor", 11/1995-12/1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Photographs with negatives: First Party of the Year "Oy, the Places You'll Go" [1/3], 08/28/1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Photographs with negatives: First Party of the Year "Oy, the Places You'll Go" [2/3], 08/28/1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Photographs with negatives: First Party of the Year "Oy, the Places You'll Go" [3/3], 08/28/1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Photographs with negatives: Gewirz Center Dedication, 04/17/1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Gewirz Center, exterior shots, 02/28/1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Photographs with negatives: Grad Wine and Cheese Party in the Sukkah, 10/10/1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: "GW Students Participate in Hillel's Birthright Israel Program", 01/2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Photograph used on Hillel's Homepage
    - Photographs with negatives: Hanging-out inside Hillel and an outdoor barbecue, 08/1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Photographs with negatives: Hillel Participates in Rock the Vote and a Meeting inside Hillel, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Hillel Staff and Student Officers, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Professional photography by Arthur Feller
    - Photographs: Holocaust Remembrance at the Quad, 04/1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Photographs with negatives: Jewish Policy Center Forum, 04/29/1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [1/4], 08/29/1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [2/4], 08/29/1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [3/4], 08/29/1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [4/4], 08/29/1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      concluding two folders in Box 5
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [1/2], 08/29/1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      continued from Box 4
    - Photographs with negatives: Kick-Off Party, a.k.a. "Up All Night" [2/2], 08/29/1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Photographs with negatives: Making Peanut Butter & Jelly and Dancing Party at Hillel, 1996 ca. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Making Peanut Butter & Jelly and Dancing Party at Hillel, 1996 ca. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Photographs with negatives: Miscellaneous black & white photographs, 1945-1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Dancing Lesson at Hillel, 04/1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Enlarged Color Copies, 1994 ca. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Photographs with negatives: Miscellaneous Party at Hillel, 1995 ca. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Party at Hillel, 1996 ca. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Photographs with negatives: Miscellaneous Lecture by a GW Faculty Member, 1995 ca. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Photographs with negatives: Miscellaneous Performance at Hillel, 1996 ca. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Photos, 1990 ca.-1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Photos, 02/1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Photos, 04/1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Photo-Ready Images in a Pictorial Collage in Hillel Capital, 06/14/1949 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Queen Margrethe III of Denmark, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Photographs with negatives: Rally in Support for the Middle East Peace Process at Lafeyette Park [1/2], 09/28/95 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Photographs with negatives: Rally in Support for the Middle East Peace Process at Lafeyette Park [2/2], 09/28/95 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Photographs: Regional Jewish Conference, Jewish Encounters with Leadership, 03/03/1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Photographs with negatives: Scott Fried, Living with AIDS, 04/27/1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Photographs with negatives: Semiformal at Hillel, 04/13/1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Photographs with negatives: Shades & Hillel Present, "Kosher Cornbread" A Dramatic Exploration of Black-Jewish Relations and Hometz for the Homeless, Food Drive before Pesach (Passover), 03/11/1996-06/30/1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Photographs with negatives: Trip to Israeli Embassy, 09/20/1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Tu B'Shevat Seder, 02/04/1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: A Wedding Ceremony at Hillel, 1993 ca. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Photographs with negatives: Yitzchak Rabin Vigil and Memorial, 11/06/1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous: unidentified prints or negatives, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Slides, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: nine boarded photographs from the 50th Anniversary exhibit, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Folder: Exhibit Photographs (neg): Originals of the photographs that were boarded for the 50th Anniversary Exhibit, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Folders (four): Oversized photographs from a dance, 1945 ca.-1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Two of the photographs have a corresponding negative inside the folder
    - Carousel: 80 slides from Hillel [currently missing], 03/20/1997-04/03/1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Currently missing. The images are primarily from the late 1940s/1950s or the 1990s and are in both black & white and color. See box 6 folder 10 for slides of Hillel events and people.
    - Carousel: 59 slides from Hillel [currently missing], 03/20/1997-04/03/1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: front and back of newspaper clippings and issues of the Hillel Capital Commentary, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      The majority of both can also be found in the Clippings Series file, and the Publications series file, Hillel Capital Commentary. There is also one black and white photograph and two letters of correspondence. The first letter, dated March 15, 1948, is from the George Washington University Chapter of the Intercollegiate Zionist Federation of America to the Washington Zionist Youth Commission. The second letter, dated January 1, 1949, is from the National Fund Chairman of the Intercollegiate Zionist Federation of America to the George Washington University Chapter of the Intercollegiate Zionist Federation of America
    - Lithograph Plate: with a black steal backdrop and the imprint is of the front cover of the Hillel Capital, Yearbook Edition (engraved), 1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Computer mouse pad from Hillel's 50th Anniversary Celebration, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Poster for Simon Wiesenthal's discussion of his memoirs, "The Murderers Among Us" presented by Hillel, 1980 ca. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hillel Ball of Fire Poster, 11/19/1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2014 Transfer, 1994-2014; Series 24 Subseries 2; 1 Linear Feet
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Hillel, August 4, 2014 (2014.026)
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Alternative Spring Break, Circa 2000; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Assorted photographs, Circa 2005; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Assorted photographs, 2010-2013; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Assorted photographs [1/2], 2003; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Assorted photographs [2/2], 2003; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Birthright photographs, 2005 January; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Draft capital campaign documents, Circa 2010; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Engagement approach documents, 2011; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - FreshFest, 2002; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Freshmen welcome event, 2008; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Hillel mailings [1/2], 1996-1998; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Hillel mailings [2/2], 1996-1998; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Hillel mousepad, undated; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Hillel registration documents and assorted forms, Circa 1960 - Circa 1980; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Holiday celebration doucments [1/2], 1996-2004; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Holiday celebration documents [2/2], 1994-2004; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Israel advocacy documents, Circa 2000; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Israel advocacy documents, 2002; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - JSA [Jewish Student Association] by-laws, Circa 1999; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - JSA program planning handbook, Hillel 5 year plan, high holiday, 2006-2011; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Melanie Birnholtz staff exit memo, 2004; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - News clippings, 2002-2008; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Photographs from Hillel events [1/2], 1993-1994; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Photographs from Hillel events [2/2], 1993-1994; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Plaque, 2005 May 9; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Object 1)
      General
      Plaque reads: Hillel of Greater Washington Program Award presented to George Washington University Ethiopian Cultural Night For excellence in programming and continuing commitment to a vibrant Jewish community on campus Spotlight on Jewish campus life Monday, May 9, 2005 30 Nissan 5765
    - Plaque, 2005 May 9; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Object 2)
      Plaque reads: Hillel of Greater Washington Program Award presented to George Washington University Fulfill Your Sole For excellence in programming and continuing commitment to a vibrant Jewish community on campus Spotlight on Jewish campus life Monday, May 9, 2005 30 Nissan 5765
    - Plaque, 2003; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Object 3)
      Award reads: The Gary Rosenthal Collection, Inc. & Hillel of Greater Washington Tzedek Art Challenge 2003 "To our future leaders for your creativity and commitment to the arts and service"
    - Plaque, 2006 May 8; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Object 4)
      Award reads: Partnership for Jewish life and learning Hillel program award presented to George Washington University SLAM AIDS Poetry and Concert benefit For Excellence in programming and continuing commitment to a vibrant Jewish community on campus Celebration of Jewish Campus Life Monday, May 8, 2006 10 Iyar 5766
    - Plaque, 2006 May 8; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Object 5)
      Award reads: Partnership for Jewish life and learning Hillel program award presented to George Washington University Women & Judaism Seminar Series For Excellence in programming and continuing commitment to a vibrant Jewish community on campus Celebration of Jewish Campus Life Monday, May 8, 2006 10 Iyar 5766
    - Poster: Ball of Fire, 1949-1964; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 1)
      This poster was most likely created by the University Archives for an exhibit at Hillel. Circa late 1990s or early 2000s.
    - Poster: GW, Zionism and Israel, 1977-1992; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 2)
    - Poster: Hillel welcomes you, 1948-1952, undated; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 3)
    - Poster: Jewish Fraternities and Sororities, 1917-1948; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 4)
    - Poster: Leadership: Hillel Advisors and Directors, 1944-2000; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 5)
    - Poster: Student Life 1960s and 1970s, Circa 1960 - Circa 1970; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 6)
    - Poster: The Last Fifty years, 1946-1996; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Poster 7)
    - Programming fliers and documents [1/2], 1996-1998; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Programming fliers and documents [2/2], 1996-1998; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Programming fliers, Circa 1999; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Programming documents, Early 2000; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Programming documents, 2005; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Programming summary, 2003-2004; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Programming fliers, 2010-2014; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - September 11th memorial info, 2011; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Student Alliance for Israel documents, 2003-2004; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - UGeW launch documents, 2011; Series 24 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- GW Band, 1931-1963; RG0115 Series 26; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of photocopies of news clippings of the GW band (Kappa Kappa Psi band fraternity), including the Malkus years, the Brusiloff years, the original band, Doris Bruffey band, Dick Willis band. The materials range in date from 1931-63.
  - Photocopies of news clippings regarding performances, Kappa Kappa Psi Band fraternity; The Malkus Years, 1931-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photocopies of news clippings regarding performances, Kappa Kappa Psi Band fraternity; The Brusiloff Years, 1936-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of news clippings regarding performances, Kappa Kappa Psi Band fraternity; The Death of the Original Band, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of news clippings regarding performances, Kappa Kappa Psi Band fraternity; The Doris Bruffey Band, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photocopies of news clippings regarding performances, Kappa Kappa Psi Band fraternity; The Dick Willis Band, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Buttons, ca.1993-1996; RG0115 Series 27; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 1)
  This series consists of various buttons of The George Washington University, including basketball, Colonial Inauguration, parents services, commencement, etc. The materials range in date from ca.1993-96.
  - Buttons, undated (Flat box 1, Folder 1)
    12 buttons. Colonials basketball; GWU, Monumental Celebration at Union Station (May 8, 1993); A Capital Investment hire GWU GRADS; Earth Week '94; GWU Family Weekend/Open House 1993; A Capital Investment hire GWU GRADS; GWU-CPA L126 AFL-CIO; GW Observes ... Black History Month; We Share the Dream ... The George Washington University; FLOC Volunteers ... Enriching the Lives of Children; GW Oh Yes, You Will; Countdown to Commencement, Monumental Celebration at Union Station (May 7, 1994)
  - Buttons, undated (Flat box 1, Folder 2)
    12 buttons. The George Washington University Columbian School of Arts & Sciences; GW DAD; GW Votes; Be Excellent to each other; GWU MOM; I'm a fan of 'Mr. GW'; Let My People Know; The George Washington University Washington DC; ASK ME ABOUT CO-OP; I Have An OCL Attitude! Commencement to service through excellence; By George! The George Washington University; Night on the S.S. Marvin Center
  - Buttons, undated (Flat box 1, Folder 3)
    9 buttons. GWU DAD The George Washington University; A Capital Investment hire GWU GRADS; Countdown to Commencement Monumental Celebration at Union Station (May 7, 1994); Monument Celebration on the Eve of Graduation; We Share The Dream George Washington University; CI!; Honor Diversity School for International Training; GW is Fourty Sixth; The George Washington University 175th Anniversary 1821-1996
- Posters, 1998-2006; RG0115 Series 28; 5 Linear Feet; 1 Linear foot (Map-folder 1)
  This series consists of posters from the Office of Student Life. The materials range in date from 1998-2003.
  - Starbursts fireworks at dusk Mount Vernon field, 1999 September 4; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 1)
  - Winter Hoopla with Margaret Cho, 2002 February 9; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 2)
  - Eco Conference, 2001 October 19 - 21; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 3)
  - Leadership 101 L.E.A.D. Center, undated; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 4)
  - Fesival of Faiths: Religion Week, 2001; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 5)
  - Late Night with the President, 2005 October 24; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 6)
  - Midnight Madness '99, 1999 October 15; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 7)
  - Fraternity Rush, February 4-8, no year; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 8)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 2002 December 11; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 9)
  - Chinese New Year, 2003 February 8; Series 28 (Box 1, Poster 10)
  - John Mayer Summer tour (t-shirt), 2002 September 2; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 1)
  - 6th Annual Alpha Phi Alpha Charity Step Show, 2003 February 8; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 2)
  - Election Day, 2000 November 7; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 3)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 2003 May 1; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 4)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 1999 May 2; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 5)
  - 8th Annual Panhellenic Fashion Show, March 13, no year; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 6)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 2002 December 8; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 7)
  - National Leadership Series, October 8 - November 6, no year; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 8)
  - Stress Free Zone events, April - May, no year; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 9)
  - Exam relief at J Street, December, no year; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 10)
  - Hippodrome grand opening, 1999 December 1; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 11)
  - Marvin Gras, January 30, no year; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 12)
  - Leadership 101 tools for success, 2003 January - April; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 13)
  - Midnight breakfast, 1998 December 9; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 14)
  - Fall Fest "Got Fall Fest?" featuring redman, 2001 September 8; Series 28 (Box 2, Poster 15)
  - Illuminate opening Convocation, 1995 August 28; Series 28 (Map-folder 2, Poster 1)